Next, let's talk about increasing the size of our vocabulary.
接下来我们讨论词汇量增加的问题
&gt;&gt; Okay, I've selected some signs we can use to start making phrases.
— 好 我已经挑选了一些手势 用来组成短语
But we're going to have to choose topologies for each of them.
我们要选择每个手势的拓扑图
&gt;&gt; Well, we've already chosen topologies for I and we.
— 我们已经为 I 和 we 选择了拓扑图
What sign is next on your list?
接下来你列表中的符号是什么？
&gt;&gt; Well, let's add, want
— 我们来添加 want
[BLANK_AUDIO].
[背景音]
How many states does that look like to you?
你认为包括几个状态呢？
&gt;&gt; Well it has the onset where you bring your hands up, the actual motion for
— 包括起初你举起手来
the sign itself.
手势本身的实际动作
And then you're dropping your hands again.
然后是你再次放下手
I would say three states.
我认为是三个状态
&gt;&gt; Well how about for, need?
— 那么 need 呢？
[BLANK_AUDIO]
[背景音]
&gt;&gt; That looks similar, so I'd also use three states.
— 这是类似的 所以我也会用三个状态
&gt;&gt; Okay here's a trickier one.
— 好 这是个比较复杂的
This is an example for the sign for table.
这里有个例子是 table (桌子) 手势
[BLANK_AUDIO]
[背景音]
But, hold on, that was actually a poor example.
不过等一下 这个例子不太好
There's a better example for table.
还有个关于 table (桌子) 更好的例子
&gt;&gt; So your hands go up and down twice?
— 那么你双手举起又放下两次？
That seems like four states in this case.
这个例子看起来有 4 个状态
&gt;&gt; Yep, but to make thing even more interesting, here's another example.
— 没错 不过为了更加有趣 这里还有个例子
[BLANK_AUDIO]
[背景音]
&gt;&gt; Hold on, that time you went up and down three times.
— 等等 这次你双手举起又放下了三次
How many times is allowed?
允许出现多少次？
&gt;&gt; Well, generally you'll see the motion repeated twice.
— 其实你看到动作重复了两次
But if somebody's thinking hard about what to say,
但是如果有人认为难以理解
they might repeat the motions, stalling for time.
他们可能会重复动作 拖延时间
It's sort of like an English speaker saying or.
这类似于英语演讲者说 or (呃呃呃)
&gt;&gt; Okay, so how can we deal with that in an HMM?
— 好 那么我们如何用隐马尔可夫模型解决这个问题呢？
&gt;&gt; Well, I didn't say we always had to go from left to right with an HMM
— 我认为不能总是使用隐马尔可夫模型从左向右处理
&gt;&gt; Okay.
— 好
So we can actually make a loop in the HMM, say from the third to the second
我们实际上可以利用隐马尔可夫模型形成循环 例如从状态 3 到 2
state, so that the motions can be repeated any number of times.
这样可以重复很多次动作
&gt;&gt; Yep, you got the idea.
— 没错 你明白了我的意思
In practice, we can try lots of different typologies,
实际上我们可以尝试许多不同的拓扑图
use cross-validation with randomly selected,
使用交叉验证 利用随机选择的
training-independent test sets to settle on the best one.
独立训练的测试集 确定最好的一个
&gt;&gt; Another example of your, try the simple thing first, strategy?
— 另一个例子 you 首先从简单的开始 策略对吗？
&gt;&gt; Exactly, but in this case,
— 没错 但在这个例子中
let's try the simple typology first and only add states when necessary.
我们首先尝试简单的拓扑图 然后如有必要只添加状态
Let's look at another issue.
我们来看另一个问题
Here's an example for cat,
这个例子 cat
[BLANK_AUDIO]
[背景音]
And here's another example for cat
这是另一个例子 cat
&gt;&gt; One is one-handed, while the other is two-handed.
— 一个是单手动作 另一个是双手动作
I don't think we're going to solve that with a simple typology trick.
我认为利用简单的拓扑图技巧无法解决这个问题
&gt;&gt; We could try just a normal three-state HMM,
— 我们可以尝试使用正常三个状态的隐马尔可夫模型
then use a mixture of Gaussians to help handle the probabilities we get.
然后使用混合高斯分布 帮助处理我们得到的概率
&gt;&gt; But I think it makes more sense just to recognize these as two different
— 但是我认为把这些作为两个不同的手势进行识别
signs.
更合理
&gt;&gt; Well, how so?
— 怎么做到？
&gt;&gt; Well we could train a model for the first variation of the sign.
— 我们可以为手势的第一个变化训练一个模型
We'll call it cat one.
我们命名为 cat 1
And we'll train a separate model for the second variation and call it cat two.
然后为第二个变化训练一个独立的模型 命名为 cat 2
And then we recognize either cat one or
然后我们识别 cat 1
cat two, we'll just have our recognizer output, cat.
或 cat 2 然后输出识别程序 cat
&gt;&gt; Yep, that should solve the problem.
— 没错 这样应该可以解决问题
While this approach adds more gestures to our vocabulary,
虽然这种方法向词语中添加了更多手势
it is often the approach that results in highest accuracy,
实际上得出了更高精确度的结果
provided we have enough examples to train all the variations.
假如我们有足够的样本训练所有变化